var questions = [{
	"question": "Ile nóg ma pies z kulawą nogą ?",
	"option1": "1",
	"option2": "2",
	"option3": "4",
	"option4": "nie ma",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Czy Korwin Krull masakruje lewaków?",
	"option1": "Owszem",
	"option2": "Nie",
	"option3": "Jest feministą, nie odważyłby się",
	"option4": "Lol",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Ile jąder ma Barrack?",
	"option1": "jedno",
	"option2": "Obama",
	"option3": "Trzy",
	"option4": "Cztery",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "A",
	"option1": "B",
	"option2": "C",
	"option3": "D",
	"option4": "E",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "F ?",
	"option1": "G",
	"option2": "H",
	"option3": "I",
	"option4": "J",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "K",
	"option1": "L",
	"option2": "LL",
	"option3": "M",
	"option4": "N",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "R ?",
	"option1": "RR",
	"option2": "RRR",
	"option3": "RRRR",
	"option4": "RRRRR",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "G ?",
	"option1": "r",
	"option2": "T",
	"option3": "D",
	"option4": "V",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "F ?",
	"option1": "f",
	"option2": "ff",
	"option3": "fff",
	"option4": "XA",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "FG?",
	"option1": "RF",
	"option2": "FCV",
	"option3": "c",
	"option4": "RFTF",
	"answer": "3"
}];